[{"title": "ghvb", "cards": [{"question": "What is formoso learning outcomes...?", "answer": "the term used to describe formal systems devised for the management of people within an organization.\nEssentially, the purpose of HRM is to maximize the productivity of an organization by optimizing the effectiveness of its employees.\nThe basic mission of\u00a0human resources\u00a0will always be to acquire, develop, and retain talent; align the workforce with the business; and be an excellent contributor to the business.**\nAn Animated Introduction to the Key HR Functions\nGROUP WORK (ONE FUNCTION PER GROUP): Define and give an example :15 mins\nJob Analysis\nRecruitment and Selection\nOn Boarding\nPerformance Management\nTraining and Development\nCompensation and Reward\nLabor Relations\nSafety and Diversity\nOrganizational Development\nIMPORTANCE OF HR IN AN ORGANIZATION\nBenefits Analysis\nHR professionals are trained to conduct efficient negotiations with potential and existing employees, as well as being well-versed with employee benefits that are likely to attract quality candidates and retaining the existing workforce.\n\nGROUP WORK: 15 mins\nList down the rights and benefits of workers in the Philippines\nTraining and Development\nSince HR managers contribute significantly to training and development programs, they also play a pivotal role in strengthening employer-employee relationships."}, {"question": "How does reviewing and renewing...?", "answer": "What kind of people does the organization need, and how many?"}, {"question": "Why is more than just...?", "answer": "the continuous process of setting objectives, assessing progress and providing ongoing coaching and feedback to ensure that employees are meeting their objectives and career goals.\nGroup  Work: Performance Appraisal Form:15 mins\nResearch on a simple performance appraisal form.\nExplain to do class the key result areas of your form.\n4)  Learning and Development\nEnabling employees to develop the skills they need for the future is an essential responsibility for HR."}, {"question": "Explain how moreover, it enhances...?", "answer": "e: Individual then group work: 20 mins\nDetermine what the symbols mean.\n14 is the total score.\nConflict Management\nThey ensure that issues and conflicts are resolved effectively, approaching the problem with an unbiased attitude and encouraging effective communication to reach a solution.\n\nEstablishing a Healthy Work Culture\nA healthy work culture is pivotal in bringing out the best in employees."}, {"question": "Describe what hris can also...?", "answer": "the term used to describe formal systems devised for the management of people within an organization.\nEssentially, the purpose of HRM is to maximize the productivity of an organization by optimizing the effectiveness of its employees.\nThe basic mission of\u00a0human resources\u00a0will always be to acquire, develop, and retain talent; align the workforce with the business; and be an excellent contributor to the business.**\nAn Animated Introduction to the Key HR Functions\nGROUP WORK (ONE FUNCTION PER GROUP): Define and give an example :15 mins\nJob Analysis\nRecruitment and Selection\nOn Boarding\nPerformance Management\nTraining and Development\nCompensation and Reward\nLabor Relations\nSafety and Diversity\nOrganizational Development\nIMPORTANCE OF HR IN AN ORGANIZATION\nBenefits Analysis\nHR professionals are trained to conduct efficient negotiations with potential and existing employees, as well as being well-versed with employee benefits that are likely to attract quality candidates and retaining the existing workforce.\n\nGROUP WORK: 15 mins\nList down the rights and benefits of workers in the Philippines\nTraining and Development\nSince HR managers contribute significantly to training and development programs, they also play a pivotal role in strengthening employer-employee relationships."}, {"question": "What is hr managers contribute...?", "answer": "the term used to describe formal systems devised for the management of people within an organization.\nEssentially, the purpose of HRM is to maximize the productivity of an organization by optimizing the effectiveness of its employees.\nThe basic mission of\u00a0human resources\u00a0will always be to acquire, develop, and retain talent; align the workforce with the business; and be an excellent contributor to the business.**\nAn Animated Introduction to the Key HR Functions\nGROUP WORK (ONE FUNCTION PER GROUP): Define and give an example :15 mins\nJob Analysis\nRecruitment and Selection\nOn Boarding\nPerformance Management\nTraining and Development\nCompensation and Reward\nLabor Relations\nSafety and Diversity\nOrganizational Development\nIMPORTANCE OF HR IN AN ORGANIZATION\nBenefits Analysis\nHR professionals are trained to conduct efficient negotiations with potential and existing employees, as well as being well-versed with employee benefits that are likely to attract quality candidates and retaining the existing workforce.\n\nGROUP WORK: 15 mins\nList down the rights and benefits of workers in the Philippines\nTraining and Development\nSince HR managers contribute significantly to training and development programs, they also play a pivotal role in strengthening employer-employee relationships."}, {"question": "How does rewards include salary...?", "answer": "fying work-life balance.\n8)  Industrial Relations\nAnother function of HR is maintaining and cultivating relationships with labor unions and other collectives, and their members.\n9)  Employee Participation and Communication\nOne of the key\u00a0roles of HR\u00a0is to be a credible activist for the employees."}, {"question": "Why is this contributes to...?", "answer": "contributes to the growth of employees within the company, hence enhancing employee satisfaction and productivity.\n\nGROUP WORK: 15 MINS\nResearch on the Training Needs Assessment form which can be used by a medium size organization.\nInteractivity With Employees\nHR managers are responsible for conducting activities, events and celebrations in the organization which gives way to team building opportunities."}, {"question": "You are looking for a qualified systems administrator for your company?\nList down the questions  you intend to ask the interviewee?\nDemonstrate the interview?\n3)  Performance Management/APPRAISAL\nPerformance management is a communication process by which managers and employees work together to plan, monitor and review an employee\u2019s work objectives and overall contribution to the organization?", "answer": "trator for your company.\nList down the questions  you intend to ask the interviewee.\nDemonstrate the interview.\n3)  Performance Management/APPRAISAL\nPerformance management is a communication process by which managers and employees work together to plan, monitor and review an employee\u2019s work objectives and overall contribution to the organization."}, {"question": "Describe what what journey will...?", "answer": "the term used to describe formal systems devised for the management of people within an organization.\nEssentially, the purpose of HRM is to maximize the productivity of an organization by optimizing the effectiveness of its employees.\nThe basic mission of\u00a0human resources\u00a0will always be to acquire, develop, and retain talent; align the workforce with the business; and be an excellent contributor to the business.**\nAn Animated Introduction to the Key HR Functions\nGROUP WORK (ONE FUNCTION PER GROUP): Define and give an example :15 mins\nJob Analysis\nRecruitment and Selection\nOn Boarding\nPerformance Management\nTraining and Development\nCompensation and Reward\nLabor Relations\nSafety and Diversity\nOrganizational Development\nIMPORTANCE OF HR IN AN ORGANIZATION\nBenefits Analysis\nHR professionals are trained to conduct efficient negotiations with potential and existing employees, as well as being well-versed with employee benefits that are likely to attract quality candidates and retaining the existing workforce.\n\nGROUP WORK: 15 mins\nList down the rights and benefits of workers in the Philippines\nTraining and Development\nSince HR managers contribute significantly to training and development programs, they also play a pivotal role in strengthening employer-employee relationships."}, {"question": "What is the core database...?", "answer": "directly fed to the payroll."}, {"question": "How does describe the steps...?", "answer": "all about knowing the future needs of the organization."}, {"question": "Why is employee users access...?", "answer": "Employee users access a part of the database where they can update their personal information, review pay scales, change retirement benefit programs, update direct deposit information or download benefit election documents.\n6)  Recruitment and Retention  \nHRIS can make the recruiting process much easier for many organizations."}, {"question": "This is also related to the first HR function we listed, in which HR bridges the gap between the workforce today and the workforce needed in the near future?\n5)  Career Planning/Career Pathing\nThe fifth function of HR is career planning, guidance, and development for employees,\u00a0together also referred to as\u00a0career pathing?", "answer": "is also related to the first HR function we listed, in which HR bridges the gap between the workforce today and the workforce needed in the near future.\n5)  Career Planning/Career Pathing\nThe fifth function of HR is career planning, guidance, and development for employees,\u00a0together also referred to as\u00a0career pathing."}, {"question": "Describe what knowing this will...?", "answer": "the term used to describe formal systems devised for the management of people within an organization.\nEssentially, the purpose of HRM is to maximize the productivity of an organization by optimizing the effectiveness of its employees.\nThe basic mission of\u00a0human resources\u00a0will always be to acquire, develop, and retain talent; align the workforce with the business; and be an excellent contributor to the business.**\nAn Animated Introduction to the Key HR Functions\nGROUP WORK (ONE FUNCTION PER GROUP): Define and give an example :15 mins\nJob Analysis\nRecruitment and Selection\nOn Boarding\nPerformance Management\nTraining and Development\nCompensation and Reward\nLabor Relations\nSafety and Diversity\nOrganizational Development\nIMPORTANCE OF HR IN AN ORGANIZATION\nBenefits Analysis\nHR professionals are trained to conduct efficient negotiations with potential and existing employees, as well as being well-versed with employee benefits that are likely to attract quality candidates and retaining the existing workforce.\n\nGROUP WORK: 15 mins\nList down the rights and benefits of workers in the Philippines\nTraining and Development\nSince HR managers contribute significantly to training and development programs, they also play a pivotal role in strengthening employer-employee relationships."}, {"question": "What is the hris payroll...?", "answer": "directly fed to the payroll."}, {"question": "How does time and labor...?", "answer": "What kind of people does the organization need, and how many?"}, {"question": "Why is for the organization,...?", "answer": "the term used to describe formal systems devised for the management of people within an organization.\nEssentially, the purpose of HRM is to maximize the productivity of an organization by optimizing the effectiveness of its employees.\nThe basic mission of\u00a0human resources\u00a0will always be to acquire, develop, and retain talent; align the workforce with the business; and be an excellent contributor to the business.**\nAn Animated Introduction to the Key HR Functions\nGROUP WORK (ONE FUNCTION PER GROUP): Define and give an example :15 mins\nJob Analysis\nRecruitment and Selection\nOn Boarding\nPerformance Management\nTraining and Development\nCompensation and Reward\nLabor Relations\nSafety and Diversity\nOrganizational Development\nIMPORTANCE OF HR IN AN ORGANIZATION\nBenefits Analysis\nHR professionals are trained to conduct efficient negotiations with potential and existing employees, as well as being well-versed with employee benefits that are likely to attract quality candidates and retaining the existing workforce.\n\nGROUP WORK: 15 mins\nList down the rights and benefits of workers in the Philippines\nTraining and Development\nSince HR managers contribute significantly to training and development programs, they also play a pivotal role in strengthening employer-employee relationships."}, {"question": "Explain how such applications allow...?", "answer": "Such applications allow employers to have one-stop shopping experience for all their human resources data management needs.\u00a0\n5)  Employee Interface\nMost HRIS packages allow for an employee to have limited user access."}, {"question": "Describe what making these regulations...?", "answer": "one of the main functions of HR.\n11)  Personal Wellbeing\nHR has a function in assisting and taking care of employees when they run into personal problems."}], "card_count": 20, "created_by": "shirlz", "created_at": "2025-03-25 21:01:11"}]